Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 75, folder: 6 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Church and the Disorder of Society, Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    By World Council of Churches. Report of Section III of the First Assembly of the World Council of Churches at Amsterdam, Aug. 22-Sept. 4, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 7 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Welcome Handbook for Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
    By Wright Patterson Air Force Base. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 8 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Wurlitzer, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
    By Wurlitzer Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 9 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    By Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation. for graduates in chemistry, engineering, & business administration. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 10 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: For Your Information, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
    By Wyman-Gordon Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 11 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Wyandotte Nation-Wide: On Our 70th Anniversary, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    By Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation. Oct-Nov edition of The Chief. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 12 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: 1961-1962 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
    By University of Wyoming. Division of Adult Education and Community Service. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 13 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Amended Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
    By Wyoming State Personnel Commission. effective January 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 14 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Explore with Xerox Corporation, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    By Xerox Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 15 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Box: 75, folder: 16 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Progress and Paths of Xerox, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Notice of Annual Meeting and Proxy Statement, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The Shape and Character of Xerox, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
    By Xerox Corporation. An address by President Joseph C. Wilson before the Security Analysts of San Francisco, Thursday January 28, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: An Address by Joseph C. Wilson, President, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
    By Xerox Corporation. Thursday, February 28, 1963; The Investment Analysts Society of Chicago. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: This Is Xerox Corporation, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: A Short History of Xerox, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: An Image of Xerox Corporation, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Xerox, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Box: 75, folder: 17 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Xerox Business Products: 1976, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    By Xerox Corporation. Vol. 6, No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Corporate Contributions: The Why, the What, and the How, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Xerox World, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    By Xerox Corporation. March 1977; No. 34. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Digest, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    By Xerox Corporation. November 19, 1976; vol. 8., no. 15. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 18 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Progress Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    By Xerox Corporation. November 3, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: 1962 Shareholders Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: 1963 Shareholders Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: 1961 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: 1962 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: The Xerox Newsletter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    By Xerox Corporation. July 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: C. Peter McColough of Xerox Corp., Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    By Xerox Corporation. September 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: 1971 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Customers Receive Much More Than a Machine, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: What People Say About Xerox, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    By Xerox Corporation. folder of notes and company related information. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 19 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Specific Needs for Leadership in Management, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    By Gilbert W. Chapman. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 20 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Update of Personal Manual, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Kimble M. Williams. April 5, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sick Leave Policy, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Yale University. June 23, 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 21 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Economic Growth Center at Yale University, Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
    By Yale University. 1961-1964 Report; published in April 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 22 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between York Corporation and the Yorkco Engineering Division Employees' Association, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    By York Corporation. effective June 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement Between York Corporation and the Yorkco Salaried Employees' Association, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Box: 75, folder: 23 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 1951 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    By York Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Our Company in 1951, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    By York Corporation. annual report to employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The York Corporation's Report to Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Box: 75, folder: 24 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Strike Nobody Wanted, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    By J.L. Mauthe. July 6, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Representation of Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Representation of Employees+, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. copy. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 25 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Let's Make Steel, Publication (Box 75, Folder 25)
    By The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. facts quoted rom 1962 annual report. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 26 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Career Openings for Graduating Seniors, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Career Openings for Current Graduates and Returning Veterans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Career Openings for Jjune (1964) Graduates Only, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Management Careers at the Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: An Invitation to Consider the Career Opportunities at Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Box: 75, folder: 27 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. vol. 4. no. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. vol. 4, no. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. a special edition; March 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company. vol. 5, no. 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 28 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Silver Bay Conference on Human Relations in Industry, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
    By Y.M.C.A. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: It is Cooperative Cosmopolitan Commendable- Have You a Part In It, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Character and Efficiency, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Box: 75, folder: 29 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Why Students Should Support the General Electric Workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By Michael Harrington. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Why Students Should Support the General Electric Workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By Michael Harrington. copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Youth Committee to Support the G.E. Workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By Michael Harrington. copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The G.E. Strike and the Vietnam War: Two Separate Issues, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By Penn Kemble. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Word About Some Forgotten Americans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By Youth Committee to Support the G.E. Workers. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 30 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: A Word About Some Forgotten Americans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Please Don't Buy GE Products, Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
- Box: 75, folder: 31 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunities in Engineering and Research, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Zenith Radio Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Salary Information Sheet and Notice to Payroll, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Salary Information Sheet and Notice to Payroll, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Wage-Hour Act Classification, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: What You Get at Zenith & Employment Application Record, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: Blank Employment Form, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Blank Employment Survey, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Notice to Payroll, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Carbon Copies of Notice to Payroll, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Welcome to Zenith, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: Zenith's Plans for Future Manpower Requirements, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 12: Seniority Clauses, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Zenith Radio Corporation. February 10, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Welcometo Zenith, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Box: 75, folder: 32 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: 1950 Annual Report, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
    By Zenith Radio Corporation. December 31, 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 33 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Memo to Subscriber and Zenith's Suggestion Booklet for Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Zenith's Suggestion Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
    By Zenith Radio Corporation. copy. Item is in English.